[{"answer": "How was your day, today, sir", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Do you like the people you work with", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Effective. But to tell you the truth, I've lost my passion for work", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I work alone", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well, let's just say that sometimes I'm right. Sometimes you are", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " It's only natural...", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "It'll be depressing", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I just know", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Seventeen months ago I was posting a walk in that place, and he was there. He never saw me. But I saw him, though", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "In that place, yes", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "It's a place where religious peopl", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "They told me you're taking lithium, mom", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You have a headache", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yes, they give me headaches. I have a headache", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I have a headache. You have a headache", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You have a headache", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No, I don't have one", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I have a headache. You have a headache", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You don't have a headache. I have a headache", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "It's fine", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " I've looked at it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Wait a minut", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "So if we do his job, we're the bad guys. If we do our job, we're the good guys", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Whol", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Nothing in the omelette. Nothing at all", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You're wrong. Look at his face", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " I love. I kill", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You do not", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You don't..", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I sell biscuits to the Southland", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "It's what I do", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "The three my friend's. Three my friend's. All named my friend..", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "--she's got half the state of that plac", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Which would you rather...", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Soft. I'll take the junkie otter, clearly! I'd let the little beast scratch and claw all he wants... Okay. Would you rather make love to the candied corpse of my frien", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Too junk", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Could be. The physical substance of love", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "grosse_point_blank.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "It's something I do..", "qsentId": 40}]